maximumasp.com 2012-12-24

# MaximumASP’s Safe Harbor Data Privacy Policy

MaximumASP’s Safe Harbor Data Privacy Policy
SAFE HARBOR
Consistent with its commitment to protect personal privacy, MaximumASP declares that it
adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles embodied in the Safe Harbor Agreement concerning
the transfer of personal data from the European Union to the United States of America.
The United States Department of Commerce and the European Commission have agreed
on the Safe Harbor Principles as they are articulated in a set of data protection principles
and frequently asked questions as a means to enable U.S. companies to satisfy EU law
requirements for adequate protection of personal information transferred from the EU to
the United States. If there is a conflict between the provisions of this Privacy Policy and
the Safe Harbor Principles, the Safe Harbor Principles will govern.
DEFINITIONS
The following definitions apply to all statements throughout this Privacy Policy.
"Personal information" means any information or set of information that is transferred
from the EU to the United States, is recorded in any form, pertains to or is about any
individual, and can be linked to or used to identify that individual. Personal information
does not include information that is encoded, or publicly available information that has not
been combined with non-public personal information. Personal information does not
include information that pertains to or is about a specific individual, but from which that
individual could not reasonably be identified.
"Sensitive personal information" means personal information that reveals race, ethnic
origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, or
that concerns health or sex life. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, MaximumASP will
treat as sensitive personal information any information received from a third party where
that third party treats and identifies the information as sensitive.
THE PRIVACY PRINCIPLES
MaximumASP’s operations and processing of personal information conform to the
following Safe Harbor Privacy Principles as stated below under the heading of each
principle.
Notice and Choice
To the extent permitted by the Safe Harbor Agreement, MaximumASP reserves the right
to process personal information in the course of providing professional services to
MaximumASP’s clients and customers without the knowledge of individuals involved. If
and when MaximumASP collects personal information directly from individuals in the
EU, MaximumASP will inform them about the types of personal information it collects

from them, the purposes for which MaximumASP collects and uses it, and the types of
non-agent third parties to which MaximumASP discloses that information. MaximumASP
will also inform those individuals about the choices and means, if any, that MaximumASP
offers to limit the use or disclosure of their information.
Disclosures and Transfers
MaximumASP will not disclose an individual's personal information to third parties,
except when one or more of the following conditions is true:
    MaximumASP has the individual's permission to make the disclosure;
    The disclosure is required by law or professional standards;
    The disclosure is reasonably related to the sale or disposition of all or part of
     MaximumASP’s business;
    The information in question is publicly available;
    The disclosure is reasonably necessary for the establishment or defense of legal
     claims; or
    The disclosure is to another MaximumASP entity or to persons or entities providing
     services on MaximumASP’s or the individual's behalf (each a "transferee"), consistent
     with the purpose for which the information was obtained, if the transferee, with
     respect to the information in question:
          o is subject to law providing an adequate level of privacy protection;
          o has agreed in writing to provide an adequate level of privacy protection; or
          o Subscribes to the Safe Harbor Principles.
Permitted transfers of information, whether to third parties or within MaximumASP,
include the transfer of data from one jurisdiction to another, including transfers to and
from the U.S. Because privacy laws vary from one jurisdiction to another, personal
information may be transferred to a jurisdiction where the laws provide less or different
protection than the jurisdiction in which the information originated.
Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the
appropriate use and confidentiality of information, either for its own purposes or on behalf
of its clients, customers and business partners, MaximumASP has put in place and
rigorously enforces appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to
safeguard and secure the information that MaximumASP processes. However,
MaximumASP cannot guarantee the security of information on or transmitted via the
Internet.
Data Integrity
MaximumASP processes personal information only in ways compatible with the purpose
for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. To the extent
necessary for such purposes, MaximumASP takes reasonable steps to make sure that
personal information is accurate, complete, current, and otherwise reliable for its intended
use.

Access and Correction
If an individual becomes aware that information MaximumASP maintains about that
individual is inaccurate, or if an individual would like to update or review that individual’s
information, the individual may contact MaximumASP using the contact information
below. In every case, MaximumASP will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to
correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate. The individual
seeking to amend such information will need to provide sufficient identifying information,
such as name, address, birth date, and social security number. MaximumASP may request
additional identifying information as a security precaution. In addition, MaximumASP
may limit or deny access to personal information where providing such access would be
unreasonably burdensome or expensive in the circumstances, or as otherwise permitted by
the Safe Harbor Agreement. In some circumstances, MaximumASP may charge a
reasonable fee, where warranted, for access to personal information.
Enforcement and Dispute Resolution
MaximumASP utilizes the self-assessment approach to assure its compliance with this
Privacy Policy. MaximumASP periodically verifies that this Privacy Policy is accurate,
comprehensive for the information intended to be covered, prominently displayed,
completely implemented, and in conformity with the Safe Harbor Principles.
MaximumASP encourages interested persons to raise any concerns about its
implementation of this Privacy Policy using the contact information below. MaximumASP
will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and
disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this
Privacy Policy.
Any claim arising out of or relating to MaximumASP’s adherence to the EU Data
Directive, or the breach thereof, that cannot be resolved through MaximumASP’s internal
processes, will be settled by arbitration administered by the American Arbitration
Association (“AAA”) in accordance with its applicable commercial rules. Any arbitrator
will be either an attorney or retired judge having significant and recognized experience
with and knowledge of privacy issues and information technology. The arbitration panel
should apply Texas law, without regard to its conflict of laws principles, as well as the
Safe Harbor Enforcement Principles issued by the U.S. Department of Commerce. In
addition, the exclusive location for such arbitration will be Houston, Texas. All decisions
of the arbitration panel will be final and binding on the parties, which waive any right to
appeal the arbitration award further, to the extent an appeal may be lawfully waived.
MaximumASP is also subject to the jurisdiction of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.
CHANGES
MaximumASP may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, consistent with the
requirements of the Safe Harbor Principles or the United States Department of Commerce.
MaximumASP will post any revised privacy policy in its work places, train its employees
about such changes and how to comply with them, and will publish any amended privacy
policy on this Web site or a similar Web site that replaces this Web site.

   INFORMATION SUBJECT TO OTHER POLICIES OR STANDARDS
   MaximumASP is committed to following the Safe Harbor Principles for all personal
   information within the scope of the Safe Harbor Agreement. Certain information,
   however, is subject to policies of MaximumASP that may differ in some respects from the
   provisions of this Privacy Policy. Information subject to such additional policies includes
   information obtained from or relating to a client, customer or business partner or former
   client, customer or business partner that is subject to the terms of any privacy notice to or
   agreement with such client, customer or business partner, any engagement letter or letters
   with such client, customer or business partner, and applicable laws and professional
   standards.
   CONTACT INFORMATION
   Questions or comments regarding MaximumASP’s Safe Harbor certification and this
   Privacy Policy should be submitted to MaximumASP by mail or e-mail as follows:
MaximumASP, LLC
752 Barret Avenue
Suite 103
Louisville, KY 40204
U.S.A.
US and Canada Toll Free: 866.925.4678
International Customers: 502.899.3220
Email: abuse@maximumasp.com
